(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
[The entire content of this drama is fictitious, for entertainment only. Please watch wisely]
The first item has arrived.
[Previous Episode]
The next item will also arrive.
Very good, Sis.
Coincidentally I need money.
I plan to look for a new house.
Why?
What happened?
If I knew from the start it would be this good if I came back,
I would have gone back a long time ago.
But, you always bother me like this.
Are you afraid that Sis Prim won't be there?
I'm not bothering you.
Just want to be friends.
Being my girlfriend is not easy.
You're the picky one.
You better go back and have fun with your people.
Are you jealous of Kris?
That moment was truly beautiful.
But, I will make it more beautiful now.
Hey, you surprised me.
You keep looking at my face like this.
I can feel it.
I like watching you sleep.
You're like a cat.
You are like a cat.
All day curling up and sleeping without paying attention to me.
Am I like a cat?
Of.
Will it curl?
Like this?
Meow, meow.
Hungry not?
I will make food for you.
But, you can only cook the basics.
Like fried eggs
and sausage.
Hungry, but more willing to hug you to sleep like this.
Like this.
Not working today?
I have to work today, but I can work at home.
Why?
In that case,
I will make breakfast for you.
Last night you took care of me.
I also want to take care of you.
This morning I was the main chef.
Guaranteed not to lose from yesterday.
Can't go.
Prim.
So cute.
Of.
Is this still edible?
This is the secret recipe.
Ouch, Prim.
Eh, Bambi.
Are you ok?
Sorry, there was a slight technical error.
It doesn't matter.
Initially I wanted to make healthy food.
The results are all messy.
Come on, let me taste it.
Hmm.
It feels good.
Is it true?
Of.
What happened?
Hmm, there was a bit of an accident.
good morning
Wait, Friends.
Bringing a girlfriend to stay at home,
weren't planning on telling me?
I also pay rent.
I have the right, right?
Bambi.
Look, he's not in denial about his girlfriend.
Welcome to officially joining the Sappho Association. [Note: Sappho means love between women]
Just admit it in the room.
I'm just a little sister on the outside.
Hey, Friends.
How could you do that to him?
Give him some status.
It should be clearer to him.
Right, right?
- Correct. - Okay.
Don't make me dismantle you. How did you curse Bambi back then?
Have you ever cursed me?
- No. - Have you ever cursed at me?
Min, what did he curse me?
- Cursing you... - Just say it straight away.
Swearing at you why it's so cute.
Be honest.
Don't.
We just eat out, we don't cook for ourselves anymore.
- Come on. - It's definitely true.
Look.
Learn to make out like your friends.
Ouch.
Come on, quickly.
♪ Rules of love, no falling in love with you ♪
♪ I know, but I don't want to hear ♪
♪ But, I want more ♪
♪ Just thinking about you ♪
♪ Girl, girl, girl ♪
♪ Forbidden to love you ♪
♪ Because I like girls ♪
[Girl Rules]
[Troublesome Girl]
Take it to table 6.
Please sit.
- Table 6. - Mother.
Hah?
Table 2, red curry stir-fried crispy pork.
Long beans replaced with mustard greens, plus half boiled fried egg.
Good.
Table 4, train fried rice.
Clear chicken tomyam soup, not spicy.
Hah?
Tomyam is not spicy,
Can it still be called a tomyam move?
Ask if it's tomyam or clear soup.
Tomyam is more interesting, Mother.
Okay.
Why are there so many people today?
It's quite a lot.
Bring to table 3.
Made according to the customer's request, dear?
The half-boiled fried egg with crispy edges has arrived.
Thank You.
Which table is this for?
Table 6, sir, hurry.
Hello, Uncle, Aunt.
Uh, hello.
Why come?
I came to the restaurant to eat.
If not, do you practice yoga?
Today many people.
If you come to trouble, go home first.
I didn't come to mess around.
You also don't answer your calls.
Sending messages is also not answered.
There's really nothing to talk about.
Today is very busy.
You go home first.
I don't have time to deal with you here.
- Sister. - Go home first.
Want mustard greens, crispy pork, fried egg.
Cooked on the inside, don't burn on the outside.
Also want to stir fry minced green chilies, only green chilies.
Good.
Hah?
Hey.
What do you want?
Excuse me, what would you like to order?
Eh.
Saute the minced green chilies, only the green chilies.
Only green chilies?
Can.
Want mustard greens, crispy pork, fried egg.
Cooked on the inside, don't burn on the outside.
Don't burn it inside and out.
What do you want to drink?
Black coffee.
A glass of black coffee.
Iced milk tea.
A glass of iced milk tea.
It tastes very good, this is my favorite restaurant.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, can we take a photo together?
Because I really really like you.
Can.
Yes.
Very beautiful.
Good grief.
Look at the camera, ouch.
Wait a minute.
Give it to me, I'll do it myself.
It's okay, I'm helping you.
That way, you'll have time to explain it to me.
There's nothing to talk about, it's very clear.
It's not clear, because you misunderstood.
Uncle, Aunt, here are the orders.
Oh, today come help me be a servant, son?
Can.
I've seen Gorya lately always complaining about being tired.
Oh, what are you tired of?
He just helped me today.
Why complain?
Mother.
Look.
Today our restaurant will be famous.
There are famous models who come to help serve food.
Right, honey.
Our business will definitely be a great success.
Go ahead, work fast, don't keep customers waiting.
Oh okay.
Everything.
Just say what you want today.
If you want to take a photo together, you can also call me.
Photo together, I want to take a photo together.
I want it here too.
Good.
Honey, even higher.
Here.
Famous models rarely come to restaurants, they have to be conspicuous.
Thank you, son.
Today food in restaurants sells very quickly.
If I have time, I will often come to help.
You can come every day, I welcome you anytime.
Remember to take photos with friends.
Mom, you're overreacting.
Not excessive.
I'll go up first.
Good.
No thanks at all?
I have invited many customers for you.
The restaurant is full every day, don't be too narcissistic.
Can you now say why you didn't pick up the phone?
Jealous of Krystal?
You are crazy.
It should be recorded in the Guinness World Records.
Your stubbornness
maybe also number 1 in the world.
Krystal and I actually dated for a while.
But they didn't get along, so they decided to be friends.
Honestly, I don't understand
with people who can be friends with your ex.
If it were me, breaking up would be breaking up.
Don't get in touch anymore, I can't tell the difference.
I can see that someone like you is also just stubborn.
Hey, just slept a few times.
Don't think you understand me enough.
No need to know you from birth.
But, I can see who is jealous.
Sorry.
Ready.
Nona Bambi.
After returning, never saw a doctor.
Looks more enthusiastic than before going abroad.
I've been having fun lately.
It's like feeling the joy of life again.
Want to do many things, brain full of project plans.
Now still insomnia?
No.
Sleep soundly, wake up refreshed.
Yes, that's good.
Can you talk to a doctor?
What makes you look so happy?
Maybe you've made up with your ex.
Wah.
Love it, Sis.
The rooms are very spacious.
The color is also very energetic.
I have lots of ideas for decorating rooms.
I saw straight away that it was your taste.
Brother really understands my heart.
Don't rush into decisions.
If you like, I will negotiate with him.
Sis, what's wrong with you?
It doesn't matter.
I just want to cry.
Maybe you're going to menstruate.
Ouch.
It's okay, Sis, I understand you.
I used to be like this too.
But, I didn't cry, I just felt annoyed when I saw everything.
Sis, quickly eat something sweet.
Otherwise, people around you will definitely suffer.
Everyone's body is different, maybe my hormones are out of balance.
To be honest, my period has been very light lately, but my stomach hurts a lot.
Want to see a doctor, Sis?
You are too busy working.
You also have to maintain your health.
That is true.
It's been a long time since I had a gynecological examination.
I'm relieved.
I thought I did something to make you cry.
You can only make Big Brother laugh.
[Second day]
This time the concept,
we will tell a couple of female lovers.
We will start from a love story, break up,
until the story makes up for them.
I want the atmosphere to be more realistic.
Hopefully it fits the song.
Director Prim thought about this story,
really reached my heart.
I've experienced something like this too.
Never an old love that passes.
Director Prim also had the same experience, right?
Oh, just a story about acquaintances.
I really like the atmosphere and story.
But, are you planning to find someone to play him?
One of them is you, Miss Kris.
Do you have candidates for anyone else?
Just forget it.
I'm not good at acting.
Does Miss Kris have a candidate to play her?
Let Shasha act as well.
He is my ex.
Yes.
So, who do you want to play him?
We have prepared...
I want to make Shasha and Gorya a couple.
Can you, Gorya?
Come on, be the female lead of the video clip.
I think Shasha and Gorya's chemical reaction
would be very interesting.
I'm a stylist, not an actress.
I'm afraid I won't be able to act.
It's okay, I think natural acting like this is good.
And I believe in Director Prim's abilities.
In my opinion, Director Prim can make the audience believe
Shasha and Gorya are lovers.
Good.
Has the patient had sexual intercourse before?
Once.
When was the last time?
Doing with women also included?
Including.
The doctor will start the examination.
Just relax.
Don't be nervous.
Hello, what's wrong Sis Da?
All invoices?
Oh, that's when I took him home.
But, now that the documents are at the old house, can I go home and get them?
Want to use it tomorrow?
I'll take care of it now.
How are you, Sis?
The doctor said there was no big problem.
Stress affects hormones.
Sis, you work too hard.
Gotta find some time to rest, Sis.
If I don't take you to see a doctor,
Brother must have gone to the shooting location again.
Look.
Without you,
Sis Prim can handle it too.
Of.
But, now there is another new problem.
What's up, Sis?
I have to go back to Park's house to get the tax documents.
Forgot to take it with me when moving.
Can't ask him to take you here, Sis?
Must try to communicate.
But, I don't think people like him will take him.
I've seen the news.
Ex-boyfriend who arranged to meet,
then his body was injured.
I don't believe him at all.
What if he goes crazy and hurts you again?
But, it's a very important document.
Want to use it tomorrow.
Anyways gotta go pick it up.
I will keep you company.
He... I think he would be angrier.
Previously he really hated you.
I am not afraid.
Let him know how wonderful your life is without him.
What happened now, Sis? Still have a stomach ache?
It's much better, the medicine the doctor gave is definitely useful.
Cut.
Everything stops first, stop.
Hmm, both of you.
I think the feelings could be deeper.
According to the story, you two should be madly in love right now.
Because this is the initial stage of the relationship.
Just imagine.
Waking up in the morning to see your girlfriend, seeing your loved one.
I don't mind.
But, I have to ask if Gorya can.
I don't know if he has experience in this area.
Things like this can also rely on imagination, Sis.
Acting must come from within.
New audiences will believe it.
Good, Sis.
I will act like I already loved each other in a previous life.
OK, let's try again.
Shasha, Gorya.
Everyone prepares, one more version.
Scene one, take two.
Start.
Playing this isn't difficult, right?
Don't you usually see me when you wake up?
That's a bed partner.
The person being played is a lover.
It takes a lot of acting.
Then act well.
Don't let the Director get jealous there.
You agreed to act, wasn't it to make the Director jealous?
Don't think I don't know.
You've conspired with friends,
so that I can shoot a video clip.
'Cause you know this is the plan,
but you still agree.
That means you like it too, right?
I like money, don't like you.
Certain?
Cut.
Passed.
Don't need a kiss?
No need.
After all, there is no need either.
So, now rest, Sis?
Of.
OK, everyone, today take a 30 minute break.
There are still many more scenes.
Kids, hurry up and eat.
Let's eat.
Hmm, How Prim.
There was someone delivering goods here earlier.
Who? Deliver what?
[Hope my director is always healthy and his ideas are limitless]
[Salmon food support for the director]
Surprise.
How? Like?
I lined up a Michelin chef especially for you.
Thank You.
But, does it need to come to this?
Look, there's even a signboard.
I'm not a famous artist.
Of course it's necessary.
The production team's work was very tiring.
You have to eat delicious food,
just have the energy to continue working.
Everything.
Come on, let's eat, today Kak Prim is treating me.
Please order, don't hesitate.
Thank you, Sis Prim.
Thank You.
Look, I'm not just for you.
But, also for the sake of all the crew.
Work hard and eat delicious food.
You can always find an excuse.
Even though I'm very awkward, I also have to defend you.
What's awkward?
Having such a cute girlfriend,
attentive and knows how to please.
Should feel proud.
Aren't you proud?
Thank You.
Ayo.
Let's order.
What do you want to eat?
That is, each menu order one portion.
Will not run out.
Eat a lot.
These are all your favorites.
You always eat irregularly.
You sleep well too.
Daily protein intake is either sufficient or not.
Do you know how much protein each day humans need?
Every day for every kilogram of body weight you need to intake one gram of protein.
Since when did you become a nutritionist?
Since having a director boyfriend.
So, know to care for you and understand you.
Now you are still the same as when you were at school.
Oh, protein.
Ah, open your mouth.
If I were still like before,
why do you still want to be my girlfriend?
Don't know.
Maybe understand you better.
Want to see you happy in the field you love.
Bringing you to realize your dreams, removing all obstacles.
If there are obstacles in the future,
I'll take care of it.
There's no need to do that.
I also never thought of asking anything from you.
But, if you take care of me it will make you happy,
then do it.
Besides, I also like to be pampered.
If so, start with protein.
It's one gram.
♪ Try one more time ♪
♪ It shouldn't hurt any more ♪
♪ I'm so evil ♪
♪ But, can you forgive me? ♪
♪ Try one more time, see how it goes ♪
♪ Keep spinning, don't change ♪
Halo.
I'm Woonsen.
Want to check Shasha's schedule?
To be honest, the kid's schedule has been really busy lately.
But, if you really want, I can help you check the schedule.
Just might have to give me more hard work money personally.
Give me cash, just transfer it to me.
No need to withhold taxes.
This already gives you price friends, really.
Because the schedule is usually very difficult to arrange.
Guaranteed not to disappoint you, Shasha is great.
Later I will help you check the schedule.
OK, I'll send it to you later.
OK, thank you very much.
This scene, the two of you are making cakes together.
The acting is more intimate.
Ayo.
Ready, camera and voice recording.
Second scene, first take, first time.
Start.
The right person has entered, he will not be jealous of you.
Do not interfere in other people's affairs.
Just pay more attention to yourself.
The manager just didn't realize he was cheated.
What do you mean?
I mean your manager.
The closest people are even the scariest.
This scene looks familiar.
Like we did before.
We have to make use of our past.
You can't just talk without evidence.
It was Brother Woonsen who made me famous.
He wouldn't do something like that.
I just said what I heard.
What's the point of me slandering him?
It's not like you're dating at all.
When I was with Prim,
much more romantic than this.
More enthusiasm, the acting is too boring.
More enthusiasm.
Bambi.
Why? No need to record sound either.
Cut, Joy, then change the camera position.
Uh, Sis Prim, someone is looking for you.
Who?
He says your father.
Why come to the shooting location?
I told him not to come.
Tell him to go home immediately.
Joy.
Of.
Can the camera be closer?
Is Prim's father coming?
Yes, outside.
I'll take care of it.
Quickly bring the camera closer, quickly.
Hurry here, son.
Why our payment amount first
not the same as the one I received?
Very little.
Has this been cut according to our agreed percentage?
Hello, Uncle.
Halo.
I'm Bambi, Prim's boyfriend.
That boyfriend you've been dating since college?
Been dating for a long time.
Prim never asked you to meet me.
What's wrong, Uncle? Prim is working.
I have business with Prim.
He didn't pick up my call,
so I came here.
Told me the same thing.
I'll take care of it.
Why are you so nice to me?
Even though we are no longer lovers.
But, we are still friends.
Promise me you won't run away and disappear again.
Won't go away.
I will keep you company.
Cut.
Good job today, done.
See you soon.
- See you later. - See you later.
Good job today.
Thank you both so much.
And also Gorya,
you could say that you have done it very well
for people who are shooting video clips for the first time.
Thank You.
Even though it is very difficult, I will also try to do it.
Hopefully the results will be good, Sis Prim.
I've sacrificed a lot.
Thank You.
Prim.
I want to ask.
What is it?
Is my schedule difficult to find?
Yes, a little.
But, Kak Woonsen will help manage it.
What is it?
In that case...
How much do you have to pay Kak Woonsen to get my schedule?
Eh...
I don't know this.
Have to ask Min.
But, as far as I know...
Have to pay 50,000 baht to get the schedule.
If you need help,
just say it.
And thank you for today.
Oh, Bambi.
Where are you going? I thought you went home quietly.
There's something to talk about.
You are amazing, Shasha.
Your acting is very similar to Prim.
Wait.
Not me, I made up the story.
Don't pretend.
This kind of atmosphere
obviously exactly the same as our college days.
But unfortunately, Gorya and I are not very similar.
Prim, I'm waiting to see the final result.
I'll go first, Bambi.
See you soon.
Only 50% is original.
The other half I made it up.
Is it true?
I'm waiting for the video clip to be shown.
Actually there are many of our stories in it.
Today you are amazing.
can i stay at your house tonight
Sleeping with you is very good.
Of course soundly.
Because you hugged me all night
and I can't sleep.
What can be done?
Because you yourself like to be my pillow.
Thank you for today.
Very good.
Why would I want to meet you here?
I don't know why I feel unbelievable.
I told him to send it, but he wouldn't.
So, you have to take it yourself.
A person like him definitely has a plan.
If he does something to you,
I will definitely teach him a lesson.
Relax, don't worry.
I know how to deal with it.
Can't you come alone?
He just accompanied me.
Give me the documents.
Are you dating?
Oh, you broke up with me
because of dating a woman?
Being a lesbian is more exciting, right?
You are exaggerating.
I broke up with you because of your problems,
not because of other people.
If you knew from the start you were a lesbian,
why did you deceive me?
People have to learn.
Today you like this, tomorrow you can like anything.
It doesn't need to always be the same.
Want me to take you upstairs?
I will make you stop being a lesbian.
It's because of your mouth.
- He doesn't want you. - Hey.
- Give it to me - What is this?
Let go, Park.
Hey, Preaw.
What is this?
Come here.
Come with me upstairs.
Park, I said let go.
No.
Let go.
Don't be stubborn.
Ayo.
If you don't let go, I'll electrocute you.
I really will.
Stop it first.
What happened?
This bastard bullies women.
I want to see the CCTV footage.
I want to report to the police.
There's nothing, Sis.
Take this, your document.
And quickly leave my apartment.
- Thank You. - Thank You.
Doesn't it hurt?
It's okay, Sis.
Isn't it delicious?
Of.
Is it dry yet? It has been dried for a long time.
Hey.
Of?
Aren't you too cruel? Don't talk to your father.
There's nothing to talk about.
Also come to ask for money.
Every time it comes when there is a problem.
But, I remember you once told me
that your father is your hero.
So people often say,
don't try to meet your heroes, because you will be disappointed.
It's either hero or hell.
You even gave me a chance.
Why not try giving your father one chance?
I remember you once told me,
the person who made you interested in music,
the person who makes you interested in films,
the person who made you want to become a director,
the person who bought you your first camera,
is your father, right?
Can.
But, the person who left me, my sister and my mother,
is also that hero.
Whatever you say.
I just want you to try to let go of some things.
Huh.
If you can only say that to other people, you can do it yourself?
You are the best at this little thing.
Hey.
Finally you came back to me.
Can you sleep with me every night?
If you sleep with me,
I don't need sleeping pills anymore.
Yes.
But...
Actually whether you can sleep or not is discussed again.
But it will slowly decrease.
Soon all that remains is to sleep in each other's arms, then say good night to each other.
Don't.
Can't be like that.
People who love each other must always be enthusiastic.
Do you know the reason most lovers break up?
Because it doesn't matter about things like this.
Of.
Okay.
I will never get bored with you.
dating you,
I can't guess your tricks.
I'm nervous for a moment,
very exciting for a moment.
In that case...
I have to find a new trick to surprise you.
What do you want?
Is sleeping like this comfortable?
Of.
Because I'm a cat, meow.
♪ Try one more time ♪
♪ It shouldn't hurt any more ♪
♪ I'm so evil ♪
♪ But, can you forgive me? ♪
♪ Try one more time, see how it goes ♪
♪ Keep spinning, don't change ♪
♪ Hearts will still be hurt accidentally ♪
♪ But, you are my darling ♪
[Public Service Center, Integrated Services]
But, he hurt my friend.
Want to drag my friend up.
If the security guard hadn't come in, who knows what would have happened now.
He hurt me too.
My arm turned red.
So defending him, what is the relationship between the two of you?
Friend.
Just this scratch, right?
I don't think there's a big problem.
I think it's just plain jealousy.
I think you two should have a good talk with him.
And the important thing is
you guys took the initiative to look for it.
I went to do something,
not letting it hurt us.
So, there's nothing we can do?
All I can do is write in my diary.
Just like this?
Why not solve it before the problem occurs?
Do we have to wait until something worse happens before it can be resolved?
Look at my girlfriend.
Ouch.
So, are you actually friends or lovers?
That is not important.
- Calm down, Preaw. - I want to know too.
If an actor or politician reports,
will you pay more attention to it?
Hah?
Or should it be like an internet celebrity?
Sis, bring your cell phone here.
Record the video.
That's enough, Preaw.
Enough.
It doesn't matter.
Then, I'll record it in the diary.
Good.
Just like this, Sis?
As a woman, you have to take care of yourself.
Otherwise, whatever happens,
he'll think I deserve it.
[Bang Luang City Police Station]
Sorry, Sis.
I was too angry.
It doesn't matter.
I know you are worried about me.
Then, why are you crying?
Are your hormones still raging, Sis?
I thought you would recover after taking the medicine.
I'm not crying because I'm menstruating.
I just realized it.
How could I put up with such a bad guy all this time?
Why I don't know
is there a good person like you waiting for me?
So, an unlucky day like this isn't that bad.
What are you laughing at?
There isn't any.
But, it's really moving, Sis.
Seeing you cry, like a kindergarten child.
Don't make fun of me.
This.
Eating a little sweet food will make you feel better.
I don't know if Prim is finished working now.
Hopefully he won't have to work overtime.
Because it's like this, Sis.
Don't think about work anymore.
The doctor told you to reduce stress.
Shasha, listen to my explanation.
This document...
This...
You organize my schedule so it's full every day,
Is it because of receiving this money?
Why?
30% still not enough?
I also have my own expenses.
Gas costs for driving.
Assistant fees, fees to look after you.
Your appearance and makeup costs when attending an event.
All this is for you.
That cost,
Clients will pay separately.
Don't think I don't know.
And the cost for the appointment.
Everything has been transferred to your account, right?
I deserve it.
I'm the one who brought you into this industry.
Your mother also entrusted you to me.
But, my mother didn't tell you to cheat me out of my money.
That's it, Sis.
We'll just get here.
We live our own lives.
Do you think you can survive? Nobody helps you.
Sis, you don't need to worry about me.
I can stand here,
not just because of you.
Master.
I'll wait and see.
[WINNING Badminton]
Ouch.
Up here first, I want to rest for a while.
What? Is this enough? I'm not tired yet.
I'm tired, let me rest for a while.
Rarely exercise and lack of sleep.
So, very tired.
Last night I saw you wake up and change jobs.
Ouch, because that's when I suddenly got an idea.
Of course you have to immediately get up and do it.
Otherwise, you will forget.
Next time, tell me before going to bed.
I will note and remind you.
Apart from being my nutritionist who monitors my diet,
so now you will also be my secretary?
Can.
Must work at an office desk.
Should also work for you.
Ayo.
Come if you dare.
Of?
Hey.
- You take advantage of opportunities. - You should also be taught a lesson.
I once said I could take care of myself.
Actually having you by my side is always better.
I told you,
no one can care about you,
take good care of you.
Come on, take a photo.
Ayo.
A short break.
Once again.
Help me massage.
Need me to help with photos?
Hmm, that's okay.
Only...
Just selfies.
Let me help with photos.
The photos taken will also look good.
Seeing you guys so intimate, are you lovers?
Can.
You guys are so cute.
Sorry, if I seem rude.
Actually, I'm also a lesbian.
Coincidentally looking for a sports partner.
Oh, actually I just started playing this again myself recently.
My name is Aerie.
Bambi.
Prim.
Good.
Let me help you take photos.
Ayo.
I'm very good at taking photos.
Good.
Oh, how cute.
You guys are so cute.
Here, look.
If we meet again, we can say hello.
I'm also looking for a workout partner.
I go first.
You are really very popular.
Not only at the bar, in the office, even on the badminton court.
I can't help but be jealous.
Are you jealous of me?
Why be jealous?
We've made up.
No matter who approaches in any way.
No matter what happens, I will choose you.
This couple is so cute together, right?
Of.
Very cute indeed.
But, I also want to know
how long can they love each other.
Oh my, this looks so delicious too.
This, this and this.
Want to eat everything.
Thank You.
Eat ice cream after playing badminton.
Looks like we're really going to start a diet.
Oh, I'm so tired.
Want to add a little sweetness.
Want to add sugar?
Ah.
- Prim. - Very delicious.
- Ah. - Prim, give me some.
Eat
BaiPo called, I picked up the phone first.
Of.
Hmm.
Is it true?
Very fresh, Sis.
Good.
That's how it used to be.
Prim, that's delicious.
Did you give my father money?
Of.
How much?
200.000 baht.
200,000 baht, Bambi?
Why?
When your father came looking for you, you were busy.
So, I'll help you take care of it.
Your father needs money.
I am your girlfriend.
I also just want to help.
Only 200,000 baht,
can be returned later.
It's not a matter of how much money.
I know you are very rich.
But, can you not solve my problem?
Especially about my father.
Me too...
Just want to see you working happily.
Don't want you to get dizzy.
That way, you can work well.
But, it's not your responsibility to make me happy.
And you don't have to solve my problems either.
I will take care of my own problems.
Listen.
Even though we've made up,
Nor does it mean that you can decide everything for me.
Uh, Prim, I'm sorry.
I don't know.
I very much...
I love you, Bambi.
But sometimes, I also feel tired of you.
It's closed.
Ouch, what are you doing here?
I already fired Kak Woonsen.
Did he say anything?
Nothing, just bringing up his kindness to me.
How dare he?
I don't know how much money he conned.
In the future I need someone to organize my schedule.
It's not difficult to find it.
Everyone wants to work with you.
Do you really think like that?
I'm also a little unruly.
Usually Kak Woonsen will help me take care of it.
Otherwise, I might have been hated by everyone in the industry.
Just look for it slowly, you will definitely find it.
can i stay at your house tonight
Can't.
You have your own home, luxurious and comfortable.
Go home and sleep at your house, come on.
I don't want to sleep alone, afraid I'll think carelessly.
Otherwise, I'll go play and bring people home.
I don't want to do that.
Hey.
If you want something to happen here, absolutely not.
Go home, come on.
I just want to sleep with you.
I promise not to touch you.
Someone like you?
The clothes are very cute.
Can you give it to me?
No way, here's to try.
Wait until it really sells, I'll give it to you.
Thank You.
Your room is very beautiful.
There are small accessories everywhere.
What's beautiful?
What a mess.
Similar to you.
It looks a lot of business, but it's also very beautiful.
Are you complimenting me?
Of.
This.
Do not take it wrong.
Telling you to sleep here because I feel sorry for you.
I know.
I didn't think too much.
This is called friendship.
Don't think too much.
Just a manager.
I'll find a new one for you.
You
angry with him because of money problems?
Nope.
Actually he can take as much as he wants.
But, what makes me sad is
because of the people I trust
instead it turned around to hurt me.
Correct.
You should check new people carefully.
Chasing his ancestors until the 18th generation.
This is outrageous.
I'm serious.
If anyone cheats me, I will put him in prison.
A small and firm person like you,
I'm sure you can do it.
It's time to sleep.
I still have work tomorrow morning.
Ouch.
Is this really your room?
Always crashing, crashing every day.
Is there any medicine?
Go to sleep.
See what? Spin over there.
So that you don't change your mind,
want to do something other than sleep.
Master.
No wonder I still believe in you so much.
Can it be discussed?
What discussion?
Can you hug me?
Can't.
I ask.
Just a short hug.
I just want to feel
feeling needed by people.
Just like this.
Just hug.
♪ Enough is enough ♪
Hey.
♪ When we lay together ♪
♪ Who do you think of me as a replacement ♪
♪ Tell the truth ♪
♪ Before you want to act as you please ♪
♪ Please create boundaries ♪
♪ And don't cross it ♪
♪ We crossed that line, huh? ♪
♪ Tell me, we'll cross the line ♪
Are you sure?
[Next Episode]
This kiss will probably change us both.
I know my words are too harsh.
But, if you slept with Shasha just to tease me,
I think you are too cruel.
Really wish there was someone like you to take care of me.
Are you willing to come take care of me?
If we love someone,
should have revealed it so he would know.
Is that woman your girlfriend?
Don't be someone else who disappoints the family.
Do you want to blackmail me?
It's better called a business negotiation.
♪ Because I like girls ♪
♪ Girl, girl, girl ♪
♪ Forbidden to love you ♪
♪ Because ♪
♪ Because I like girls ♪